sheer
indefatigability makes me a feared opponent in any realm of human which is my saying it's a
saying from my
father but it's basically saying unmatched perspicacity so the ability to always
pay attention
perspicacity is perception so unmatched I'm always paying attention to everything all the
time and sheer
indefatigability I don't become tired makes me a feared opponent in any realm of
human endeavor so
a man who always pays attention and never gives up is a feared opponent no matter
what no matter
what no matter what you're fighting against nobody else is going to wake up and care more about your
life than you if
you if you won't wake up every day and say I need to get rich
nobody else is
going to wake up and say I need to make him rich yeah nobody else is going to do it
for you so if you
don't think it nobody else is going to think it which means nobody thinks it
so it's down to
you right only you're the person you're the only person on the planet who can think